Rick Whitesell Record Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
Rick Whitesell Record Collection
1930s - 1980s
NPKMC-332-172
75 Linear Feet
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
Rick Whitesell
Rick Whitesell turned a childhood passion into a diverse musical career. His love of music led him to assemble a collection of records, or more appropriately, a collection of music, spanning five decades, dating back to the late 1920s. The collection consists of over 3,500 records and follows the development of music for more than fifty years. Also included in the collection are issues of "Goldmine" magazine, where Rick served as an editor and feature writer, as well as some audio and video tapes containing interviews and performances.
Collection Overview
The Whitesell Collection consists of discs tracing the development of black music in America as well as other genres of music. Included in the collection are several issues of "Goldmine" magazine, a music magazine where Rick worked as editor and feature writer, as well as audio and videotapes containing interviews and performances.
The Whitesell family donated the collection to Marist College.
Historical Note
The Rick Whitesell Record Collection has been characterized as one of the most comprehensive private collections of its type in the country. Tracing the development of black music from the turn of the century to the late 1950s, the collection consists of seven, ten, and twelve inch discs whose numbers span into the thousands. Early artists such as the Mills Brothers, the Southernaires, and the Charioteers are all represented in the collection. The Whitesell Collection also contains a broad cross-section of works by such premier groups as the Delta Rhythm Boys, Fred Astaire, Les Paul, Ella Fitzgerald, and the most successful of the jubilee groups, the Golden Gate Quartet.
It is important to remember that Rick Whitesell was more than just a record collector. Rick became a music historian. His talents were fully utilized at "Goldmine" magazine, a publication for record collectors. As editor and feature writer, Rick was able to formalize his studies and knowledge into insightful articles about important areas of America's cultural growth. "Gold mine" is also a part of this collection as issues can be found dating from the mid 1970s to late 1980s. Rick's expertise served as an important resource to many. Collectors, musicians, filmmakers, independent writers, and other music publications that needed small or substantial amounts of information would contact Rick for assistance. Any special consideration Rick received was used to further explore America's musical growth, correct historical inaccuracy ies he uncovered, or help those in the business. When he learned of older musicians who had never received royalty payments, he directed them to the proper songwriting associations for assistance. Rick's selfless giving lives on by the donation of his collection to Marist College for the purpose of providing future scholars with the resources to continue his work.
There are no restrictions on this collection
Arrangement of the Collection
These records are organized into nine series: 1) 10" Discs, 2) 12" Discs, 3) 7" Discs, 4) Audio Tapes, 5) Audio Reels, 6) "Goldmine" and Other Publications, 7) Video Tapes, 8) Books, and 9) Miscellaneous.
Materials are arranged alphabetically.
- 1. 10" Discs, 1; 15 linear feet Boxes: 1 - 24 Folders: 1.10.1 - 1.10.1090
  Alphabetical by artist
  - Roy Acuff&His Smoky Mountain Boys, Record Label: Columbia (1, Box 1)
    - Gone, Gone Gone (But Not Forgotten), 1
    - Let Me Be the First to Say I'm Sorry, 2
  - Marie Adams, Record Label: Peacock (2, Box 1)
    - He's My Man, 1
    - Alone, 2
  - Larry Adler, Record Label: Decca (3, Box 1)
    - Hand to Mouth Boogie, 1
    - Begin The Beguine, 2
  - From Gershwin to "Le Grisbi" Grand Prix du Disque, Record Label: Angel (4, Box 1)
    - From Gershwin, 1
    - It Ain't Necessarily So, 2
    - Bess, You Is My Woman Now, 3
    - Prelude No. 2, 4
    - Someone To Watch Over Me, 5
    - from Paris, 6
    - Le Grisbi, 7
    - My Heart Is A Violin, 8
    - Genevieve, 9
    - Pam-Pou-De, 10
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (5, Box 1)
  - Tony Allen&The Champs, Record Label: Specialty (6, Box 1)
    - I, 1
    - Nite Owl, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (7, Box 1)
  - John&Lucky Allison with Sawyer's Minute Men Ballads of the American Revolution and the War of 1812 ( five record set), Record Label: Victor (8, Box 1)
    - Yankee Doodle, 1
    - The Boston Tea Tax, 2
    - Free America, 3
    - Unhappy Boston, 4
    - The White Cockade, 5
  - John&Lucky Allison with Sawyer's Minute Men - Disc 2, Record Label: Victor (9, Box 1)
    - Ballad of Bunker Hill, 1
    - The Death of Warren, 2
    - Johnny Has Gone For A Soldier, 3
    - Riflemen's Song At Binnington, 4
  - John&Lucky Allison with Sawyer's Minute Men - Disc 3, Record Label: Victor (10, Box 1)
    - Nathan Hale, 1
    - Cornwallis's Country Dance, 2
    - The Capture of Major Andre, 3
  - John&Lucky Allison with Sawyer's Minute Men - Disc 4, Record Label: Victor (11, Box 1)
    - Hunters of Kentucky, 1
    - Ye Parliment of England, 2
    - The Constitution and the Guerriere, 3
    - Hey Betty Martin, 4
  - John&Lucky Allison with Sawyer's Minute Men - Disc 5, Record Label: Victor (12, Box 1)
    - The Chieftain's Bride, 1
    - The Bombardment of Bristol, R.I., 2
  - Andrews Sisters, Record Label: Decca (13, Box 1)
    - Hit The Road, 1
    - Ferryboat Serenade, 2
  - Andrews Sisters, Record Label: Decca (14, Box 1)
    - Beer Barrel Polka (roll out the barrel), 1
    - Well All Right (tonight's the night), 2
  - Andrews Sisters, Record Label: Decca (15, Box 1)
    - Nice Work If You Can Get It, 1
    - Bei Mir Bist Du Schon, 2
  - Andrews Sisters With Bob Crosby's Bob Cats, Record Label: Decca (16, Box 1)
    - Long Time No See, 1
    - Begin the Beguine, 2
  - Andrews Sisters With Gordon Jenkins and His Orchestra, Record Label: Decca (17, Box 1)
    - I Can Dream, Can't I?, 1
    - The Wedding of Lili Marlene, 2
  - Andrews Sisters with Vic Schoen and His Orchestra, Record Label: Decca (18, Box 1)
    - Toolie Oolie Doolie (The Yodel Polka), 1
    - I Hate to Lose You, 2
  - Andrews Sisters with Vic Schoen and His Orchestra, Record Label: Decca (19, Box 1)
    - Whispering Hope, 1
    - Lovely Night, 2
  - The Angels, Record Label: Gee (20, Box 1)
    - Glory of Love, 1
    - It's You I Love Best, 2
  - Patti Anne, Record Label: Aladdin (21, Box 1)
    - Baby, Baby, I'm In Love With You, 1
    - Shtiggy Boom, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (22, Box 1)
  - Louis Armstrong Satchmo Serenades, Record Label: Decca (23, Box 1)
    - I Get Ideas, 1
    - A Kiss to Build a Dream On, 2
    - Cold, Cold Heart, 3
    - Because of You, 4
    - La Vie En Rose, 5
    - C'est Si Bon, 6
    - Maybe It's Because, 7
    - I'll Keep the Lovelight Burning, 8
  - Gene Austin, Record Label: Victor (24, Box 1)
    - Ya Gotta Know How To Love, 1
    - Bye, Bye Blackbird, 2
  - Gene Austin, Record Label: Victor (25, Box 1)
    - The Lonesome Road (duel listed), 1
    - Frank Crumit - Wake Nicodemus, 2
  - Mildred Bailey, Record Label: Crown (26, Box 1)
    - It's Never Too Late to Pray, 1
    - Can't Help Lovin' Dat Man, 2
  - Pearl Bailey, Record Label: Columbia (27, Box 1)
    - Ma! He's Making Eyes At Me, 1
    - Don't Sit On My Bed, 2
  - Pearl Bailey, Record Label: Columbia (28, Box 1)
    - Tired, 1
    - Fifteen Years, 2
  - Charlie Barnet&His Orchestra, Record Label: RCA Victor (29, Box 1)
    - Leapin' At Lincoln, 1
  - Dick Barrow (duel listed), Record Label: Decca (30, Box 1)
    - Down At the Cabin Inn, 1
    - Jimmy Strange - Yas Yas Yas, 2
  - Count Basie&His All American Rhythm Section, Record Label: Columbia (31, Box 1)
    - St. Louis Blues, 1
    - Cafe Society Blues, 2
  - Count Basie&His Orchestra, Record Label: Vocalion (32, Box 1)
    - Don't Worry 'Bout Me, 1
    - What Goes Up Must Come Down (And Baby You've Been Flyin' Too High), 2
  - Count Basie&His Orchestra (dual listed), Record Label: OKeh (33, Box 1)
    - One O'Clock Jump, 1
    - Cab Calloway&His Orchestra - Minnie the Moocher, 2
  - Basin Street Boys, Record Label: Racy (34, Box 1)
    - Come, John, Come, 1
    - Come, John, Come, 2
  - The Ba You Boys, Record Label: Checker (35, Box 1)
    - Bambalaya, 1
    - Dinah, 2
  - The Beale Street Boys, Record Label: MGM (36, Box 1)
    - Baby Don't Be Mad At Me, 1
    - Wedding Bells (Are Breaking Up That Old Gang Of Mine), 2
  - The Bees, Record Label: Imperial (37, Box 1)
    - Toy Bell, 1
    - Snatchin' Back, 2
  - Big Three Trio, Record Label: Columbia (38, Box 1)
    - I'll Be Alright Some Day, 1
    - Reno Blues, 2
  - Big Three Trio, Record Label: Columbia (39, Box 1)
    - Just Can't Let Her Be, 1
    - Since My Baby Been Gone, 2
  - Big Three Trio, Record Label: Columbia (40, Box 1)
    - Big Three Boogie, 1
    - Evening, 2
  - Big Three Trio, Record Label: Bullet (41, Box 1)
    - You Sure Look Good To Me, 1
    - Signifying Monkey, 2
  - Birmingham Jubilee Singers, Record Label: Columbia (42, Box 1)
    - Do You Call That Religion, 1
    - Home In That Rock, 2
  - Birmingham Jubilee Singers, Record Label: Columbia (43, Box 1)
    - Glory Hallelujah, 1
    - He Died On Calvary, 2
  - Birmingham Quartet, Record Label: Columbia (44, Box 1)
    - Raise a Rukus Tonight, 1
    - Watermelon On The Vine, 2
  - The Blenders, Record Label: Decca (45, Box 2)
    - The Masquerade Is Over (I'm Afraid), 1
    - Little Small Town Girl (With Big Town Dreams), 2
  - The Blenders, Record Label: MGM (46, Box 2)
    - If That's The Way You Want It Baby, 1
    - I Don't Miss You Anymore, 2
  - The Blenders, Record Label: National (47, Box 2)
    - I Can Dream, Can't I?, 1
    - Come Back Baby Blues, 2
  - Archie Bleyer, Record Label: Cadence (48, Box 2)
    - Till They've All Gone Home, 1
    - Eh, Cumpari, 2
  - Blue Jay Gospel Singers, Record Label: Trumpet (49, Box 2)
    - Shall I Meet You Over Yonder, 1
    - Pilgrim of Sorrow, 2
  - Blue Ridge Quartet, Record Label: Gotham (50, Box 2)
    - Hold On, Brother, 1
    - Peace In The Valley, 2
  - Bon Bon and His Buddies, Record Label: 20th Century (51, Box 2)
    - When Your Old Wedding Ring Was New, 1
    - Don't Forget To Cry, 2
  - Bon Bon&The Red Caps Trio, Record Label: 2 copies Joe Davis (52, Box 2)
    - Truthfully, 1
    - Better Stop Playin' Around, 2
  - Johnny Bond&His Red River Valley Boys, Record Label: Columbia (53, Box 2)
    - Divorce Me C.O.D., 1
    - Rainbow at Midnight, 2
  - Millie Bosman, Record Label: Cat (54, Box 2)
    - Your Good Doin', 1
    - Really Satisfied, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (55, Box 2)
  - Eddie Boyd, Record Label: Chess (56, Box 2)
    - Life Gets To Be A Burden, 1
    - Don't, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (57, Box 2)
  - Sister Emily Bram, Record Label: Savoy (58, Box 2)
    - Blessed Assurance, 1
    - We'll Understand, 2
  - Big Bill Broonzy, Record Label: Conqueror (59, Box 2)
    - Key To The Highway, 1
    - Conversation With The Blues, 2
  - Big Bill Broonzy, Record Label: Conqueror (60, Box 2)
    - Rockin' Chair Blues, 1
    - That Number Of Mine, 2
  - Big Bill Broonzy, Record Label: OKeh (61, Box 2)
    - She's Gone With The Wind, 1
    - Why Should I Spend My Money, 2
  - Big Bill Broonzy Folk Blues, Record Label: Emarcy (62, Box 2)
    - John Henry, 1
    - Crawdad, 2
    - Bill Bailey, 3
    - Make My Get Away, 4
    - Blue Tail Fly, 5
    - Bessie Smith, 6
    - Leroy Carr, 7
    - Richard Jones, 8
  - Brooks Brothers, Record Label: Diamond (63, Box 2)
    - St. Louis Blues, 1
    - If Somebody Ever Breaks My Heart, 2
  - Charlie Brown&His Band, Record Label: Aladdin (64, Box 2)
    - Once There Lived A Fool, 1
    - Black Night, 2
  - Clarence "Gatemouth" Brown, Record Label: Peacock (65, Box 2)
    - Boogie Uproar, 1
    - Hurry Back Good News, 2
  - Dizzy Brown&The Dancing Tambourines, Record Label: Teen (66, Box 2)
    - Jada, 1
    - Cecilia, 2
  - Dusty Brown, Record Label: Parrot (67, Box 2)
    - He Don't Love You, 1
    - Yes She's Gone, 2
  - Nappy Brown, Record Label: Savoy (68, Box 2)
    - Love, Baby, 1
    - Am I, 2
  - Nappy Brown, Record Label: Savoy (69, Box 2)
    - Is It True - Is It True, 1
    - Two Faced Woman, 2
  - Roy Brown&His Mighty, Mighty Men, Record Label: Delux (70, Box 2)
    - Butcher Pete, part 1, 1
    - Butcher Pete, part 2, 2
  - Ruth Brown, Record Label: Atlantic (71, Box 2)
    - If You Don't Want Me (I Don't Want No Part Of You), 1
    - Love Contest, 2
  - Ruth Brown, Record Label: Atlantic (72, Box 2)
    - The Tears Keep Tumbling Down, 1
    - I Would If I Could, 2
  - Ruth Brown, Record Label: Atlantic (73, Box 2)
    - Have A Good Time, 1
    - Daddy, Daddy, 2
  - Cliff Bruner&His Boys, Record Label: Decca (74, Box 2)
    - The Girl That You Loved Long Ago, 1
    - Jessie, 2
  - The Cabineers with The Bill McRae Trio, Record Label: Abbey (75, Box 2)
    - Whirlpool, 1
    - You're Just A Great Big Deartache, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (76, Box 2)
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (77, Box 2)
  - Mr. Calhoun, Record Label: Zynn (78, Box 2)
    - Hello My Friends, Hello Pal, 1
    - On The Sunny Side Of Love, 2
  - Cab Calloway&His Orchestra, Record Label: Columbia (79, Box 2)
    - Hi-De-Ho Man (That's Me), 1
    - Necessity, 2
  - Cab Calloway&His Orchestra, Record Label: Columbia (80, Box 2)
    - If This Isn't Love, 1
    - The Honeydripper, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (81, Box 2)
  - Cab Calloway&His Orchestra, Record Label: OKeh (82, Box 2)
    - Fifteen Minute Intermission, 1
    - Rhapsody In Rhumba, 2
  - Cab Calloway&His Orchestra, Record Label: OKeh (83, Box 2)
    - A Smo-o-oth One, 1
    - Lets Go Joe, 2
  - Cab Calloway&His Orchestra, Record Label: OKeh (*33 (dual listed), Box 2)
    - Minnie The Moocher, 1
    - Count Basie&His Orchestra - One O'Clock Jump, 2
  - The Cap-Tans, Record Label: Dot (84, Box 2)
    - I'm So Crazy For Love, 1
    - Crazy About My Honey Dip, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (85, Box 2)
  - The Caravans, Record Label: States (86, Box 3)
    - Jesus Is A Rock, 1
    - Blessed and Brought Up By The Lord, 2
  - The Caravans, Record Label: States (87, Box 3)
    - The Solid Rock, 1
    - Old Time Religion, 2
  - The Caravons, Record Label: States (88, Box 3)
    - Count Your Blessings, 1
    - Stranger of Galilee, 2
  - The Caravans, Record Label: United (89, Box 3)
    - What Kind Of Man Is This, 1
    - The Man Jesus, 2
  - The Cardinals, Record Label: Atlantic (90, Box 3)
    - Two Things I Love, 1
    - Come Back My Love, 2
  - The Cardinals, Record Label: Atlantic (91, Box 3)
    - The Wheel of Fortune, 1
    - Kiss Me Baby, 2
  - Hoagy Carmichael, Record Label: Decca (92, Box 3)
    - Star Dust, 1
    - Hong Kong Blues, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (93, Box 3)
  - Thelma Carpenter, Record Label: Majestic (94, Box 3)
    - Seems Like Old Times, 1
    - A Jug Of Wine, 2
  - Thelma Carpenter, Record Label: Majestic (95, Box 3)
    - Hurry Home, 1
    - Just A-Sittin' And A-Rockin', 2
  - Benny Carter&His Orchestra, Record Label: Decca (96, Box 3)
    - I've Been In Love Before, 1
    - Mills Brothers with Benny Carter&His Orchestra - By The Watermelon Vine, Lindy Lou, 2
  - Eddie Carter Quartet, Record Label: MGM (97, Box 3)
    - Eat 'Em Up, 1
    - Don't Turn Your Back On Me, 2
  - Russ Case&His Orchestra with The Deep River Boys, Record Label: RCA Victor (98, Box 3)
    - Necessity, 1
    - Russ Case&His Orchestra with Jimmy Carroll - Old Devil Moon, 2
  - The Cashmeres, Record Label: Mercury (99, Box 3)
    - Boom Mag-azeno Vip Vay, 1
    - Don't Let It Happen Again, 2
  - The Cats and the Fiddle, Record Label: Bluebird (100, Box 3)
    - In The Midst Of A Dream, 1
    - Hep Cat's Holiday, 2
  - The Cats and the Fiddle, Record Label: Bluebird (101, Box 3)
    - Swing The Scales, 1
    - Hush-A-Bye Love, 2
  - The Cats and the Fiddle, Record Label: Bluebird (102, Box 3)
    - I'm Gonna Pull My Hair, 1
    - If I Dream Of You, 2
  - The Cats and the Fiddle, Record Label: Bluebird (103, Box 3)
    - Life's Too Short, 1
    - Part Of me, 2
  - The Cats and the Fiddle, Record Label: Bluebird (104, Box 3)
    - Killer Diller Man From The South, 1
    - Thursday Evening Swing, 2
  - The Cats and the Fiddle, Record Label: Bluebird (105, Box 3)
    - Gone, 1
    - Mister Rhythm Man, 2
  - The Cats and the Fiddle, Record Label: Bluebird (106, Box 3)
    - Until I Met You, 1
    - Crawlin' Blues, 2
  - The Cats and the Fiddle, Record Label: Bluebird (107, Box 3)
    - I'm Singing (So Help Me), 1
    - My Darling, 2
  - The Cats and the Fiddle, Record Label: Bluebird (108, Box 3)
    - Nuts To You
    - Killin' Jive
  - The Cats and the Fiddle, Record Label: Bluebird (109, Box 3)
    - Left With The Thought Of You
    - When I Grow Too Old To Dream
  - The Cats and the Fiddle, Record Label: Bluebird (110, Box 3)
    - Public Jitterbug No. 1, 1
    - I Miss You So, 2
  - The Cats and the Fiddle, Record Label: Bluebird (111, Box 3)
    - Gang Busters, 1
    - Please Don't Leave Me Now, 2
  - The Cats and the Fiddle, Record Label: Manor (112, Box 3)
    - Honey, Honey, Honey, 1
    - I'm Afraid Of You, 2
  - The Cats and the Fiddle, Record Label: Manor (113, Box 3)
    - My Sugar's Sweet To Me, 1
    - I Miss You So, 2
  - The Cats and the Fiddle, Record Label: Manor (114, Box 3)
    - That's What I Thought You Said, 1
    - The New Look Blues, 2
  - The Cats and the Fiddle, Record Label: Gotham (115, Box 3)
    - Start Talking, Baby, 1
    - I'll Never, Never Let You Go, 2
  - Cats 'N Jammer Three, Record Label: Mercury (116, Box 3)
    - Jockey Blues, 1
    - I Cover The Water-Front, 2
  - Cats 'N Jammer Three, Record Label: Mercury (117, Box 3)
    - One Hundred Years From Today, 1
    - I'm Coming Home To Stay, 2
  - The Chanteclairs, Record Label: Dot (118, Box 3)
    - Believe Me Beloved, 1
    - I've Never Been There, 2
  - The Chanteclairs, Record Label: Dot (119, Box 3)
    - Baby Please, 1
    - Someday My Love Will Come My Way, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: 2 copies Columbia (120, Box 3)
    - Oooh! Look-a There, Ain't She Pretty?, 1
    - What Did He Say (The Mumble Song), 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: 2 copies Columbia (121, Box 3)
    - So Long, 1
    - The Gaucho Serenade, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: 2 copies Columbia (122, Box 3)
    - Chi-baba Chi-baba (My Bambino Go To Sleep), 1
    - Say No More, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: 2 copies Columbia (123, Box 3)
    - When I Grow Too Old To Dream, 1
    - The Last Thing I Want Is Your Pity, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: Columbia (124, Box 3)
    - Open The Door, Richard, 1
    - You Can't See The Sun When You're Cryin', 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: Columbia (125, Box 3)
    - No Soup, 1
    - One More Dream (And She's Mine), 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: Columbia (126, Box 3)
    - Silver Threads Among The Gold, 1
    - Love's Old Sweet Song, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: Columbia (127, Box 3)
    - Hawaiian Sunset, 1
    - This Side Of Heaven, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: Columbia (128, Box 4)
    - You Make Me Feel So Young, 1
    - On the Boardwalk (In Atlantic City), 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: Columbia (129, Box 4)
    - I Can't Get Started, 1
    - Sweet Marie, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: Columbia (130, Box 4)
    - Until, 1
    - It's Too Soon To Know, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: Columbia (131, Box 4)
    - I Understand, 1
    - A Dream For Sale, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: Columbia (132, Box 4)
    - A Kiss And A Rose, 1
    - A Cottage In Old Donegal, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: Columbia (133, Box 4)
    - It Doesn't Cost You Anything To Dream, 1
    - Don't You Notice Anything New, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: Columbia (134, Box 4)
    - My Heart's On Ice, 1
    - Goodnight Mother, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: Columbia (135, Box 4)
    - Braggin', 1
    - You Walk By, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: Columbia (136, Box 4)
    - Sulvia, 1
    - I'm Gettin' Sentimental Over You, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: Columbia (137, Box 4)
    - Sylvia, 1
    - This Side Of Heaven, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: OKeh (138, Box 4)
    - Hawaiian Sunset, 1
    - Elmer's Tune, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: OKeh (139, Box 4)
    - Wrap Your Troubles In Dreams, 1
    - I Heard Of A City Called Heaven, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: OKeh (140, Box 4)
    - Cancel The Flowers, 1
    - I Got It Bad, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: OKeh (141, Box 4)
    - Tica-tee Tica-Ta, 1
    - The Train Song, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: OKeh (142, Box 4)
    - Daddy, 1
    - Down, Down, Down (What A Song!), 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: OKeh (143, Box 4)
    - The Cowboy Serenade (While I'm Rollin' My Last Cigerette), 1
    - Yes Indeed!, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (144, Box 4)
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: Decca (145, Box 4)
    - Along Tobacco Road, 1
    - Ridin' Around In The Rain, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: Brunswick (146, Box 4)
    - Water Boy, 1
    - Steal Away To Jesus, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (147, Box 4)
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: Vocalion (148, Box 4)
    - Forget If You Can, 1
    - My Gal Sal, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: Vocalion (149, Box 4)
    - Laughing Boy Blue, 1
    - Sing You Sinners, 2
  - The Charioteers, Record Label: Vocalion (150, Box 4)
    - Speak To Me Of Love (Parlez-Moi D'Amour), 1
    - Mazine Sullivan (dual listed) - A Brown Bird Singing, 2
  - The Charioteers and Pearl Bailey, Record Label: Harmony (151, Box 4)
    - Who, 1
    - Don't Ever Leave Me, 2
  - Charles and Carl, Record Label: Red Robin (152, Box 4)
    - Lucky Star, 1
    - One More Chance, 2
  - The Cherokees, Record Label: Grand (153, Box 4)
    - Rainbow of Love, 1
    - I Had a Thrill, 2
  - Bob Chester&His Orchestera, Record Label: Bluebird (154, Box 4)
    - I Wish I Had A Sweetheart, 1
    - Madelaine, 2
  - Maurice Chevalier, Record Label: RCA Victor (155, Box 4)
    - Vingt Ans (At the Age of 20) part 1 - in English, 1
    - Vingt Ans (At the Age of 20) part 2 - in French, 2
  - Savannah Churchill, Record Label: Decca (156, Box 4)
    - The Gypsy Was Wrong, 1
    - Just Whisper, 2
  - Savannah Churchill and The Five Kings, Record Label: Manor (157, Box 4)
    - Sincerely Yours, 1
    - I'm Too Shy, 2
  - Savannah Churchill and Al Killian&His Orchestra, Record Label: Manor (158, Box 4)
    - I Can't Get Enough Of You, 1
    - Too Blue To Cry, 2
  - Savannah Churchill and The Sentimentalists, Record Label: Manor (159, Box 4)
    - I Want To Be Loved (But Only By You), 1
    - Foolishly Yours, 2
  - Savannah Churchill and The Four Tunes, Record Label: Columbia (160, Box 4)
    - The Best Of Friends, 1
    - The Things You Do To Me, 2
  - Savannah Churchill and The Four Tunes, Record Label: Manor (161, Box 4)
    - How Could I Know, 1
    - It's Raining Down In Sunshine Lane, 2
  - Savannah Churchill and The Four Tunes, Record Label: Manor (162, Box 4)
    - Time Out For Tears, 1
    - The Four Tunes (dual listed) All My Dreams, 2
  - Savannah Churchill and The Four Tunes, Record Label: Arco (163, Box 4)
    - I Want to Cry, 1
    - Savannah Churchill with Lenny Herman&His Orchestra - My Baby-Kin, 2
  - Savannah Churchill with Ralph Hermann's Orchestra, Record Label: Manor (164, Box 4)
    - Don't Try To Explain, 1
    - Savannah Churchill with The Four Tunes Savannah Sings The Blues, 2
  - Savannah Churchill with Ralph Hermann's Orchestra, Record Label: Manor (165, Box 4)
    - Try To Forget, 1